hotelspro.com 2016-11-19

# Global Travel Wholesaler | HotelsPro

Thank you for visiting Hotelspro.com website. Your privacy is very important to us, and we provide this privacy policy statement to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your personal information is collected and used.

For your convenience, this website contains links to a number of other websites, both inside and outside Hotelspro.com. The privacy policies and procedures here do not apply to those sites.

The purpose of this privacy policy is to set out the principles governing our use of personal information that we may obtain about you. By using the websites, or by registering as a user of the services that we provide, you agree to this use. We ask you to read this privacy policy carefully. Any dispute which may arise over privacy will be subject to this policy, the data protection notice (if any) incorporated into this website and the provisions of Turkish law.

We may change our privacy policy from time to time. We therefore ask you to check it occasionally to ensure that you are aware of the most recent version that will apply each time you access this website.

### Personal information collection and use

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfil your requests for our products, programmes, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programmes or services that we believe may be of interest to you. Sometimes, we also use this information to communicate with you, such as when we make changes to our subscriber agreements.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorised disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Statement.

E-mail addresses may be used to inform clients of services and offers which are most likely to be of interest to them. With respect to this use of personal information, customers may at any time indicate their preference not to receive such information by changing their account settings. Or may click on a link named “Unsubscribe” which is embedded with every email sent by hotelspro.com in order not to receive future messages.

### Use of cookies

To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use `cookies.` Cookies are text files we place in your computer`s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. They can not be used to identify you. You may set your web browser to notify you of cookie placement requests or to decline cookies completely. You can delete the files that contain cookies; those files are stored as part of your internet browser.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact: [info@hotelspro.com](mailto:info@hotelspro.com)

Phone: +90 212 315 14 92 (24/7)

Prodo Travel Ltd. (DBA Met Global)  
Company Address: Mehmet Akif Cad. No: 60, K/2 Koskluciftlik Lefkosa Mersin 10 Turkey
